jamendo.com 2014-06-26

# Jamendo - Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the use of the JAMENDO Services. By using JAMENDO Services you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy. We may modify or update this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please review it periodically. Your continued use of Jamendo services after any modification of this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such modification. This Privacy Policy was updated on December 13, 2013. 

## 1\. Information we collect

You donât need to provide Jamendo with any personal information in order to visit our services. However, some services require that you register for a Jamendo account and, by doing so, you may provide us with personal information: email address, user name, password, real name, bank information, location, profile picture, etc. We also collect information from other sources when you sign in using third parties services (Facebook, Google, Twitter). This usually includes your public information on these third parties services and your email. Only some of these information are mandatory, notably in order to be able to join our commercial programs Jamendo PRO. Our services clearly state which information is or is not mandatory at the time we collect it. You may also provide personal information when you use our services by posting music, comments, participate to community discussions, etc. 

We may also collect some information automatically when you use our services: the IP address and the characteristics of your device, your browsing history and the actions made on our services, etc. These information may be either collected directly by Jamendo or through the use of third parties analytics services. In order to collect these information, we may use cookies and similar technologies. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer when using our services. These text files can be read and help to identify you when you return to our services. You can control how we use cookies on your device by modifying your browserâs cookie settings. Please note that if you set your browser to disable cookies or other technologies, you may not be able to access certain parts of our services and other parts of our services may not work properly. 

## 2\. How we use your information

The information that we collect may be used notably for the following purposes: Used to identify you when you log in on our services. Published on our services when applicable (public profile, community discussions, comments, etc.). Please keep this in mind when providing any public information. To send you updates, newsletters and email notifications about our services. To share your activities with your contacts if you are connected through third parties services (Facebook, Google, Twitter). To operate your Jamendo account and to give you access to our services. To respond to you about any comment or enquiry you have submitted. To customize your use of our services and to improve our services over time. 

## 3\. Sharing of your information

Your personal information may be shared with third parties as described below: Any personal information shared publicly (public profiles, community discussions, comments, etc.) will be available to other users. Our services clearly state which information may or may not be shared at the time we collect it. Your information may be shared with third parties who provide us with services (analytics, emailing, etc.) but only for the purpose of providing such services to us. Jamendo usersâ personal information may be aggregated in order to create statistics used to improve our services. If required by law we may disclose personal information to competent authorities. 

Your information may be transferred to third parties outside European Union and notably in United-States. You should be aware that privacy laws in other countries may not be equivalent to the laws in your country, and by using Jamendo services you consent to the transfer, the storage and the processing of your personal information outside European Union. 

## 4\. Your choices about your information

Any information you provided to Jamendo when you registered an account may be accessed, modified or deleted at any time through the settings page of your Jamendo account. Please note that deleting mandatory information may prevent you from using the related services. Concerning any information not available in your account settings you can write us at legal@jamendo.com. You can unsubscribe at any time from email updates and newsletter by clicking on the âunsubscribeâ link at the bottoms of said updates and newsletters. Some information are collected automatically when you use our services. If you do not want us to collect information in such way please do not use the Platform.
